<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[beaumont-shuttersandblindsltd]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[beaumont-shuttersandblindsltd]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2016 20:45:24 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="undefinedrss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>BEAUMONT works hard in bring quality accross the whole company giving our customers peace of mind with our blinds and shutters. All our staff are fully trained and have years of exsperiance in installing interior shutters and venetian blinds and are here to help you acheive that perfect look that you are after. Our shutters are supplied and manufactured by the world leader in shutter production utilising a combination of state of the art manufacturing with hand crafted finishing touches. The woods utilised in our hardwood shutters for example are stored for 6 months to allow the wood to settle before being kiln dryed twice in computer controlled conditions  to reduce the risk of warping and twisting. All shutters are assembled prior to shipping to ensure that all the components fit together perfectly. We work hard in keeping our plantation shutters cost very competitive so if you live in Hampshire, Surrey or Berkshire and are looking to have shutters then why book your free survey and transform your home Interior.
You will see from our images the white shutters have become very popular accross all styles of Interior shutters.</p>]]></description>
            <link>undefinedbeaumont-works-hard-in-bring-quality-accross-the-whole-compa/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">8d293c70-6a72-40fa-ba5b-7aa4cba18113</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2016 20:45:02 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>